{
    "id": "3e86f11738384797bf795409b193476c",
    "title": "First conditional clauses",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d35ee6d63c174bec9339ebca65d66461",
            "title": "First Conditional Clauses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If he doesn’t mend his ways, he ………………… in serious trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will land",
                        "would land",
                        "would have landed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you …………………. hard you will pass the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "worked",
                        "had worked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If he ………………….. now, we can all have dinner together.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrive",
                        "arrives",
                        "arrived"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you ………………… her, she will not come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't invite",
                        "don't invite",
                        "hadn't invited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I don’t meet him, I ………………….. to his mother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will talk",
                        "would talk",
                        "would have talked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If she ………………. English, she will get a better job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "spoke",
                        "speaks",
                        "had spoken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If he arrives now, we ....................... in trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would be",
                        "will be",
                        "would have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If she ………………… out the truth, she will be really angry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "find",
                        "finds",
                        "found"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I ……………… a millionaire, I will not work at all.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am",
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I ………………… the answer, I will tell you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knows",
                        "know",
                        "knew"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}